<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on D. J. Dorey Rodriguez</title>
    <link>https://dandoreyrodriguez.github.io/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on D. J. Dorey Rodriguez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dandoreyrodriguez.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Dorey Rodriguez</title>
      <link>https://dandoreyrodriguez.github.io/authors/example-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dandoreyrodriguez.github.io/authors/example-author/</guid>
      <description>A little about me&amp;hellip; Some general fiels of interest include: Economics, Statistics, History, and Data Science. More specifically, I&amp;rsquo;m interesting in leveraging data to shatter conventional wisdoms across a series of domains.
At the core of my thinking lies a belief in the heteredox. In other words, I reject that the intellectual fruit worth picking has already been picked. If it has, what are we all doing?
In my little way, I hope, via my blog posts and through my educational and professional life, to influence positively those with whom I come into contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Authors</title>
      <link>https://dandoreyrodriguez.github.io/authors/hugo-authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dandoreyrodriguez.github.io/authors/hugo-authors/</guid>
      <description>Vestibulum vel arcu Donec interdum justo sed posuere imperdiet. Quisque nec mauris eu erat mattis egestas in vitae nisl. Sed nisl augue, congue sed quam quis, tempor tempus nibh. Pellentesque accumsan in quam a interdum. Morbi iaculis venenatis lacinia. Mauris quis nisl vitae nisi mollis placerat id vel ligula. Integer vitae arcu ac leo iaculis rhoncus id vitae dolor. Fusce quis nisl tincidunt, vulputate dolor quis, mollis massa. Donec congue velit at risus cursus, eu auctor dolor rhoncus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
